https://www.limogesjewelry.com/terms-privacy#privacypolicy

Menu RingsBridalSolitairesSetsBandsMen'sClass/graduationLadiesMen'sCouplesFamilyMother's RingsGrandmotherSisterDadMen'sWeddingBandsSignetSets and WardrobesNames and initialsNamesInitialsMonogramsNames w/ BirthstoneKidsRings/Religious/Inspirational/MemorialFashionStackablesSingle BirthstoneNecklacesCouplesFamilyMotherGrandmotherSisterDadMen'sSets and WardrobesNames and initialsPlaques/ BarsCut-out namesMonograms/ InitialsSpecial OccasionsNoveltyFamilyKidsLocketsReligious/ Inspirational/ MemorialFashionLayered-MultiClass/graduationClass PendantsGraduation GiftsBridal PartySingle BirthstoneNames w/ BirthstoneMedicalCollectionGiftsOtherKey RingsBlack Hills GoldMother's GiftsMen'sRingsBandsWeddingSignetSpinner BandsClass RingsNecklacesBraceletsAccessoriesEarringsHoopsDropsButtons/ StudsCrawlersSetsFashionBraceletsFamilyCouplesKidsMedicReligious/ Inspirational/ MemorialMen'sMultiplesAnkletsNames and InitialsPlaques/ BarsCut-out namesFamilyBridesmaidsFashionNoveltySingle BirthstoneMedicalNames w/ BirthstoneWeddingRings for herSolitairesSetsBandsRings for himBridal PartyNecklacesBraceletsNEW ARRIVALSRingsMen'sLadiesNecklacesMen'sLadiesBraceletsMen'sLadiesEarringsFashionSets and WardrobesClearanceRingsNecklacesBraceletsEarringsFashionSets and WardrobesNewarrivalsThe Limoges Jewelry Holiday ShopNecklacesRingsBraceletsGraduation GiftsEarrings
Account
Home
Terms and Privacy
About Us
Ordering
Order Tracking
Shipping
Returns
Safety/Security
Discount Codes and Groupon Vouchers
Contact Us
Terms and Privacy
We recognize that our online customers are concerned about their personal information and how it will be used. So we have done our very best to make ordering from Limogés Jewelry a safe and hassle-free experience!
Order Technology
Orders placed on our site are encrypted with SSL (Secure Socket Layers) technology. When placing an order with us, you are on our secure server where you can enter your personal information without fear of it being insecurely transmitted to someone else. Check this by looking for the lock symbol at the bottom of your browser window. You will see that this symbol appears as soon as you click to submit your order, indicating you are on a secure site. The information you send through our site can be trusted to arrive safely and privately.
Your Personal Information
Limogés Jewelry collects information that you volunteer in order to process your order, to inform you of special offers, and so that you may receive superior customer service. We do not share your e-mail address with anyone outside of Limogés Jewelry other than when necessary to fulfill your order. On occasion, we may share other information with very carefully selected partners in order to provide you with outstanding special offers, but we will only do so with your consent.
Additional Information We Collect
From time to time, we use a third-party service provider to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. They may collect anonymous information about your visits and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other Web sites to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major web sites. Absolutely no personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. They do not know the name, phone number, address, e-mail address, or any personally identifying information about the user. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this anonymous information used by our third party service provider, please click here: www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
If you do not want to receive promotional emails from Limoges Jewelry, please write to:
Limogés Jewelry
WWW Remove
31 s Mitchell Ct.
Addison, IL 60101
Recently Viewed No recently views items Clear All
